（ナルト）お前
いったい誰なんだってばよ？
Who are you really?
俺は　誰でもない。
誰でもいたくないのさ。
I'm nobody.
I don't want to be anybody.
ただ　月の眼計画を
成せれば　それでいい。
I just want to fulfill
Project Tsuki no Me.
That is enough.
絶望しかないこの世界に
存在する価値はない。
It's not worth living in this world
where only despair exists.
お前たち人柱力は
尾獣を取り付けさせられ→
You Jinchuriki had Tailed Beasts
forced upon you
絶望ばかりを見てきた。　違うか？
and you've only
experienced despair…
Am I wrong?
お前たちだったら　この絶望を
少しは理解できるだろう。
Surely, you can understand
a little of my despair…
尾獣と一緒にいることが→
Who the hell are you to decide…
不幸せだと
勝手に思い込むんじゃねえよ！
that having a Tailed Beast
inside me makes me unhappy?!
テメエにとっちゃあ
価値のねえ　この世界でも→
Even if this world is
worthless to you,
勝手に戦争まで起こしておいて
誰でもねえなんて→
you really think you can get away
with starting a war
そんなんでごまかして
通用すると思ってんのか！？
and trying to play off
that you're a nobody?
頭きた。
You piss me off…
ぜってぇ　その面を
ひっぺがしてやる！
I'm gonna rip that mask off of you!
（ビー）まずは　俺が行く。　ウィー！！
I'll go first! Wheee!
この面　はがすには…。
Taking this mask off of me…
骨がおれるぞ。
won't be so easy.
八尾　九尾
俺はお前らを手に入れて→
Eight Tails… Nine Tails…
You shall be mine…
月の眼を手に入れる！
and I'll achieve
Project Tsuki no Me!
九尾も八尾も
お前なんかにゃやらねえ！
We're not gonna let
you have Nine Tails or Eight Tails!
どういうことだ？
ヤツら尾獣を抜かれたはずだろ？
What's going on?
I thought their Tailed Beasts
were extracted from them?!
（八尾）穢土転生で
よみがえったあとで→
They were probably made back
into Jinchuriki
もう一度　人柱力に
されたんだろうな。
after they were reanimated…
尾獣たちも　今までと
様子が違うのを感じる。
I can also sense that
the Tailed Beasts are
a bit different from before too…
気をつけろ　ビー。
Be careful!
どうした？
お前も感じるのか　違和感。
You too? Getting bad vibes?
コイツはなめたらアカン。
Gotta be careful for our lives
((老紫：溶遁　灼河流岩の術！
Corrosion Style!
Scorching Rocks Jutsu!
なるほど
人違いではないようだな。
This isn't a case of
mistaken identity I take it…
わしの弱点も
研究済みというわけか。
My weaknesses have already been
carefully researched.
ならば　これならどうする？
So now, how will you deal with this?
（鬼鮫）体を溶岩に？
He turned his body into lava?!
一筋縄では
いかないということですか。
He's trickier than I thought.
《水遁　大爆水衝波！》
Water Style!
Giant Exploding Water Shock Wave.
口だけではないようだな。
He's not all talk either.
I wish you'd just allow yourself
to be captured
おとなしく捕まって
くれるわけにはいきませんかね。
without all this fuss.
What a pain.
厄介ですね。
（イタチ）戻ったか。
ええ。
You're back.
Yeah, but having to bring
him back without killing him
殺さずに生け捕るってのが
面倒でしたがね。
was quite bothersome.
少し降ってきましたね。
It's starting to rain.
Looks like it'll storm.
荒れそうだな。
木陰で雨をしのぎましょう。
体が冷えますよ。
Let's take cover under a tree.
Or we'll catch a cold.
Our leader is waiting
for word of his capture.
リーダーが連絡を待っている。
我々の捕獲が完了し次第→
Immediately after that,
the sealing of
the Three Tails and Four Tails
is to occur simultaneously.
三尾と四尾を
同時に封印する手はずだからな。
少しぐらい
待たせておけばいいんですよ。
We'll make him wait a little.
封印を始めたら　どうせ→
Because once the sealing starts,
we'll be working nonstop.
しばらくは働きづめなんですから。
死にそうだな。
年寄りは丁寧に扱え。
He seems to be near death.
You really should treat
the elderly with care.
コイツを知らないから
そんなこと言うんですよ。
You say that because
you don't know him.
This Jinchuriki who uses
四尾の溶遁を使う　この人柱力は
そんなタマじゃないですよ。
the Corrosion Style Jutsu of
the Four Tails
isn't what you think he is.
You didn't fight him,
直接　戦っていない　あなたには→
so you don't know
what I just went through.
(私の苦労は
わからないでしょうがね))
Jinchuriki vs. Jinchuriki!
鮫肌も　やる気ビンビン！　了解！
Samehada is ready to fight
That's fine with me…
なら今度は
こっちからガンガン行くかい！
'Cuz I'm raring to go…
Are ya ready?
ちょっと待てって！
ビーのおっちゃん！
Hold it, Octopops!
《いい動きだ！》
Nice moves…
《オーケー　気づいてない　ケーオー！》
OK! She hasn't spied my…KO!
《見えてもねえのに
なんでかわせる！？
You didn't even see me,
so how'd you dodge?! Fool, ya fool!
バカ野郎　この野郎！》
それじゃダメだ！　ビーのおっちゃん！
That's not gonna work, Octopops!
前　戦った
ペインの六道と　おんなじだ！
It's just like the time
I fought the Six Paths of Pain.
アイツらの眼　輪廻眼は
全員つながって見えてんだ！
Their eyes…
They're Rinnegan are all linked.
They're hooked up to each other!
どういうことだ？
What the hell does that mean?!
It's the same as
Nagato's Gedo Jutsu!
長門と同じ外道の術だ！
だから　６人分の視覚が
１つにつながってて…。
So they've got the eyesight…
of six guys!
クソッ　話もでき…　アツ！
Damn, I can't even talk…!
Hot!
Aw man!
It's Yugito's Rodent Hair Ball!
《やべぇ　ユギトのねずみ玉！》
追ってくるってばよ！
It's coming after us!
これは誘導！
いったん逃げるぜ　堂々！
It's like a guided missile
Time to run, let's hustle
《ユギトのヤツ　昔と動きが違う。
Yugito's moves are different
from before…
サプライズ！　高かった俺のマフラー半分！
Half left of my expensive scarf…
What a surprise
これじゃ　半プライス！
Now it's only worth half the price
（八尾）あの写輪眼だ。
It's that Sharingan!
あれで　こっちの動きを
細かく見切ってるな。
That's how they're able
to track us so closely!
ヤツらに瞳力が加わった分→
Their Visual Prowess is
enhancing their Jinchuriki abilities!
人柱力の能力が
おのおの上がってやがる。
更に　あの共有した視界で
人柱力６人の位置関係や→
On top of that,
with their shared vision,
the six Jinchuriki can
position themselves
攻撃のタイミングを
有利に運びやがってんな。
and time their attacks
with more precision.
ビー！　ナルトと話をさせろ！
Bee! Let me talk to Naruto!
ヨー！
Yo!
ナルト　アイツら
２つの瞳力と尾獣の力を→
Naruto… They're cleverly combining
the two types of Visual Prowess
and their Jinchuriki abilities.
うまく使ってきやがる。
ここも　恐らく　バレてるぞ。
どうする？
They're probably on to us too.
What do we do?
人柱力６人を
１人ずつ止めていくしかねえ。
We have no choice
but to take down
six Jinchuriki one by one!
長門のときと　おんなじなら
みんなチャクラで操られているはずだ。
If it's the same as
that time with Nagato,
they're all controlled by chakra.
あのときは　そのチャクラを
受信するために→
Back then, in order to get chakra,
みんな　体のどこかに
黒い受信機が刺してあった。
black receivers were stuck
to their bodies.
なるほど　ソイツを
引き抜くか壊しさえすれば→
I see…
If we remove it or destroy it…
外道の術とやらは
解けるってことか。
the Gedo Jutsu would be undone.
しかし　そりゃ厄介だな。
But that's going to be
a problem.
こっちの攻撃を
当てるのも難しいってのに。
It's hard enough landing
a blow on them.
どこにあるかも　わからねえ
その黒い受信機を　ピンポイントで…。
And we can't even pinpoint
where these black receivers are.
（ビー）あれか…。
You mean, that thing?
Huh?
どれ！？
Where?!
ユギトの胸元を　ガン見して点検！
Take a close look around Yugito's bosom
And you'll see that black protrusion
そしたら　黒い出っ張りを発見！
最初は使いこまれた…　グハッ！
At first, I thought it was her ni--!
《丸見えは不感　チラリズムで実感》
When they're flaunted,
it's unappealing
But just a little glimpse,
it's a good feeling
《お前…
この戦いが　世界の未来を→
This battle is going to
determine the future.
左右するっちゅうときに
必死で何を…》
And you're only thinking about…
あれだってばよ！
That's it!
なら　他のヤツも確かめる。
I'm going to go check out
the others.
Wait, Naruto!
（八尾）ナルト　待て！
Our attacks don't work,
and we can't catch them…
《攻撃が当たらねえし
捕まえられねえんなら…》
《攻撃を食らって
捕まえりゃいい！》
Hot!
I'll just have to put up
with their attacks and grab them!
螺旋丸！
Rasengan!
《やっぱ　ここか！》
I knew it was here!
《なら　このまま…》
Then… I'll just…!
大丈夫か？　２人とも。
Are you two all right?
イテッ…。
Ouch…
ビー　コイツら相手に
林の中じゃ　逆に不利だ。
Bee… We're at a disadvantage
fighting them in the woods.
お前にとっちゃ
余計　視界が悪くなる。
Your field of vision is narrowed!
（八尾）わかってんな？　ビー。
《おう…　よう…》
You get me, don't you, Bee?!
Oh…yeah…
ここらの森
全部　吹っ飛ばしちまえ！！
Blow up the entire forest!
（ビー）八尾が　サビの
キラービーだぜ　俺様が！
I'm the Killer Bee and
Eight Tails is here with me!
Wheee!
ウィーッ！！
おっと！
（ビー）振り落とされんなよ　ナルト！
ここからが本番だぜ　なんと！
Don't fall off of me, Naruto
Cuz' now, the real fight's a go!
（八尾）尾獣八巻き！
Eight-Tailed Beast Twister!
あ…　あぁ～！
SHINOBI
ビー殿は　早くも尾獣化したようだ。
It seems Lord Bee has undergone
the Tailed Beast
transformation already!
大きな八尾のチャクラを感じる。
I sense the immense chakra
of the Eight Tails!
感知から見てると
少し　押されているようだ。
It feels like they're on
the defensive!
このままでは
少し　まずいかもですね　正直。
Things aren't looking
too good, are they?
Frankly…
（いのいち）しかし　五影のほうは
マダラをおさえられてる。
However, the Five Kage
have Madara on the defensive!
We're doing okay for now!
今のところは問題ない。
（シカク）五影が揃ってんだ。
そうでなければ　困る！
The Five Kage are working together.
They have to have the edge!
各部隊の状況は！？
What's the status of each company?!
第１　第２部隊は
もう少しで　敵をせん滅のもよう。
The First and Second Companies
are on the verge of
annihilating the enemy.
（ダルイ）あと　２７！
Only 27 more…!
２６！　２５！
26! 25!
だりぃけど…　一気にいくぜ！
I'm feeling tired, but…
I'll give it one more try…!
（黄ツチ）あと少しで
ここも　カタがつく！
Just a few more and
we'll be done here!
これ　黒ツチ！　先走るな。
Hey! Kurotsuchi!
Don't run off on your own!
（黒ツチ）
まどろっこしいんだよ　親父！
You're too slow, Dad!
残りものは全部　アタイに任せな。
Leave the rest…to me!
土遁　開土昇掘！
Earth Style! Erupt!
うわ～！
第３部隊において
穢土転生は　残り２人。
The Third Company is down
to two Reanimations.
Out of all the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist,
忍刀七人衆も
鬼灯満月を残すのみとなります。
only Mangetsu Hozuki is left.
（ガイ）コイツらの相手も
そろそろ　飽きてきたな。
I'm getting bored of
fighting these guys.
（カカシ）あぁ。
Yeah…
《カカシ：霧隠れ　忍刀七人衆。
The Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist…
桃地再不斬。
Zabuza Momochi,
林檎雨由利。
Ameyuri Ringo,
栗霰串丸。
Kushimaru Kuriarare,
通草野餌人。
Jinin Akebino,
無梨甚八。
Jinpachi Munashi,
西瓜山河豚鬼。
Fuguki Suikazan…
残るは…　鬼灯満月》
The only one left is…Mangetsu Hozuki.
（ミフネ）今こそ
侍道を見せるときぞ！
Now's the time to show them
the Way of the Samurai!
（カンクロウ）傀儡使いとしての忍道を
見せてやるじゃん！
Let's show 'em the Ninja Way
of Puppet Masters!
（いのいち）第５部隊は　まだ
少し　手間取っているようです。
It appears the Fifth Company
needs a little more time…
But there's no doubt that
they have the upper hand!
だが　優勢なのに
変わりはありません。
All right!
よし　第１　第２　第３　第５部隊の
各戦況のケリがつきしだい→
Tell the First, Second, Third
and Fifth Companies
as soon as they wrap up…
すぐに　ナルトとビー殿の増援へ
向かうように伝えてくれ！
They are to head over to
assist Naruto and Lord Bee!
青殿！　座標は？
What are their coordinates, Lord Ao?
す…　すげぇ…。
W-Wow…
倒れてんぞ！
They're all knocked out!
今のうちに封印しちまうぞ　ビー！
Seal them now, Bee!
ビーのおっちゃん
封印術　持ってんのか？
Hey, Octopops!
You know a Sealing Jutsu?!
杭で操られていようが
何しようが　関係ねえ。
It doesn't matter
if those rods are
controlling them or not!
We'll just tie them up
with Ink Clones!
墨分身で卍固めだ。
（ビー）封印術　オクトパスホールド！
Sealing Jutsu! Octopus Hold!
あれか！
ビーの封印術のひとつだ。
So that's it!
It's only one of Bee's Sealing Jutsu!
Just like that and on
a count of three…
あのまま　カウントスリー。　つまり３秒で
墨が体全体を完全に覆い→
Namely, in three seconds,
the ink will completely cover
their bodies and harden,
固まって動きを止める。
incapacitating them!
動けなくしてから
胸の杭を引き抜けばいい。
Once they're immobile,
we can remove the rods from their chest!
１…　２…。
– One!
– Two!
さ～！
– Three!
アハハッ　すげえ感じで封印…　した？
That was an amazing sealing…?
いや　すげえ感じで
敵がパワーアップ…　したな。
No… It was amazing
how the enemy powered up…
いけ。
あのお面野郎。
Go…
That masked bastard!
地面に隠れてやがったのか。
He was hiding underground!
（フウ）蟲食い！
（ユギト）猫爪！
（ウタカタ）蛭間。
（ビー）イテッ！
強アルカリ液だ！
皮膚を溶かされてるぞ。
ビーのおっちゃん！
（やぐら）珊瑚掌！
うわっ！　なんだ　これ！
ナルト！
（老紫）花果山！
うっ…。
ヤバイ　コイツらが今の状態で
尾獣化できるとは思わなかった。
（八尾）ナルト　ここはいったん引いて
立て直すことにするぞ。
（ハン）角折り！
フン。
《動けねえ…》
んなろう！
同じ人柱力でも
６対２では　分が悪そうだな。
この手が触れたら　俺の勝ちだ。
《ヤバイ…》
激！　木ノ葉金剛力旋風！
ナルトをおとりに
俺が実体化するタイミングを狙ったか。
余計な邪魔を。
カカシ先生に　ゲキマユ先生！
フッ　２匹増えたところで
何も変わらん。
俺の持つ瞳力と
尾獣の力の前ではな。
こっちにも写輪眼がある。
そして　木ノ葉の気高き
碧い猛獣もな。
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
美空ひばりです。
では最後まで
ごゆっくりお楽しみください。
（宮本）『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！　にっぽんの歌』。
（松丸）今回は　ご覧の豪華な歌手
１２人の皆さんによる→
華麗なステージをお届けいたします。